http://www.who-rabies-bulletin.org/site-page/privacy-policy-statement

Skip to main content
HomeImprintPrivacy policy statement
Privacy policy statement
Privacy policy statement
We appreciate that you visit our pages and thank for your interest. Your privacy on the Internet is of outmost importance to the Friedrich-Loeffler-Institute and the World Health Organization (WHO). This privacy statement describes the policy concerning the gathering and sharing of visitors’ information through the WHO sponsored FLI web site.
Anonymous web site usage
In general, you can browse the site without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. The only information we gather during general browsing is from standard server logs. These include your IP (Internet Protocol) address, domain name, browser type, operating system, and information such as the web site that referred you to us, the files you download, the pages you visit, and the dates/times of those visits. The data is collected only for statistical analysis and the user remains anonymous.
Collection and distribution of personal data
Our web pages are for public information. Therefore, we do not collect, use and distribute any personal information.
External Links
For a better information service you find links to external Sites. If it is not shown clearly we will provide information that you are leaving our web pages. The Friedrich-Loeffler-Institute has no influence whatsoever on the contents, designs and privacy policies of external web sites.
Imprint
Disclaimer
Privacy policy statement
Copyright
Back to Top
